<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="hello">Hello World, BusaoActivity!</string>
    <string name="app_name">Busão</string>
    
    <!-- Splash Screen -->
    <string name="description">Splash Screen</string>
    <string name="versao">versão 1.0</string>
    
    <!-- Loading -->
    <string name="progress_msg">loading</string>
    
    <!-- Menu principal -->
	<string name="bem_vindo">welcome!</string>
	<string name="menu_localidade">locality</string>
	<string name="menu_buscar">search</string>
	<string name="menu_turismo">tourism</string>
	<string name="menu_ajuda">help</string>
	<string name="compartilhar">share</string> 
    
	<string name="bem_vindo_desc">The BUSÂO it´s an application that gives to user 
	    the perspective  of time to the next bus. In adition, informs the routes 
	    for the tourism point and allow share with social networks. Enjoy !!!!!</string>
	
	<string name="localidade_desc">In locality menu, the user has access to informations 
	    about the current city, like the tariff price. The BUSÃO covers some of the majors 
	    cities of the Northeast. The user can choose the city for the application. </string>
	
	<string name="buscar_desc">The search in the application, helps the user to find the 
	    correct bus and the routes that meet their needs. The search can be by specific 
	    line or by GPS</string>
	    
	<string name="turismo_desc">The BUSÃO also informs the routes for the tourism point 
	    of each city. So you will have more time to enjoy architectural and cultural 
	    beauties.</string>
	
	<string name="compartilhar_desc">Choice routes with tourism point and share with 
	    social networks</string>
	
	<string name="open">open</string>
	
	<!-- Menu Ajuda -->
	<string name="ajuda_pre">pre-requisites</string>
	<string name="ajuda_rotas">search routes</string>
	<string name="ajuda_onibus">search bus</string>
	<string name="ajuda_mapas">maps</string>
	<string name="ajuda_texto_pre_requisitos">It is necessary that your device has Internet access and GPS.</string>
	<string name="ajuda_texto_onibus">To search for a specific bus line (get menu> bus), select a desired row and their data will be displayed.</string>
	<string name="ajuda_texto_rotas">In the search menu > routes, mark the two points on the map you want (this may be one of your current location) and if there is a bus line that passes through these points, your data will be displayed.</string>
	<string name="ajuda_texto_mapas">In search > maps can be viewed routes marked as favorites.</string>

	
	<!-- Popup Resultado -->
	<string name="result_faltam">Missing</string>
	<string name="result_minutos">Minutes</string>
	<string name="result_inicio">Start</string>
	<string name="result_termino">End</string>
	<string name="result_empresa">Company</string>
	<string name="result_ok">ok</string>
	<string name="result_voltar">back</string>
	<string name="result_onibus">bus founded</string>
	<string name="result_result">Search result</string>
	<string name="result_mapa">map</string>
	
	
	<!-- Cidades -->
	
	<string name="cidade_titulo_inicial">you are in</string>
	<string name="texto_tarifa">Tariff Price: R$</string>
	
	<string name="titulo_campinagrande">Campina Grande, Paraiba</string>
	<string name="titulo_joaopessoa">Joao Pessoa, Paraiba</string>
	
	<string name="cidade_campinagrande">Considered one of the main poles indrustriais the Northeast Region and the largest technological hub of Latin America,
Campina Grande was elevated to city status on October 11, 1864. The city has a varied cultural agenda chain, standing up the festivities of São João,
happening throughout the month of June, the Meeting of the New Consciousness, an ecumenical meeting held during the carnival, besides the Winter Festival.
According to the sense of 2010, the population is around 400,000 inhabitants. And considered the most dynamic city in the northeast and the sixth most dynamic city in Brazil.</string>
		
	<string name="cidade_joaopessoa">Capital of the State of Paraiba, Joao Pessoa and known as the "Gateway of the Sun", due to the fact that the city be located
Ponta do Seixas, which is the easternmost point of the Americas, which makes the city was known as the place "where the sun rises first in the Americas." The municipality
and also notable for its tropical climate, and one of the capitals best quality of life in the Northeast.</string>
	    
	<string name="descricao_about">www.busaoapp.com</string>
	
	<string name="descricao_popup_cidade">Choose a city to view your routes</string>
	
	<string name="botao_confirmar">confirm</string>
	<string name="botao_cancelar">cancel</string>
	<string name="botao_ok">ok</string>
	<string name="botao_voltar">back</string>
	<string name="botao_mapa">map</string>
	<string name="botao_alterar_cidade">change city</string>
	<string name="titulo_alterar_cidade">change city</string>
	<string name="faltam">missing</string>
	<string name="minutos">min</string>
	
	<!-- MAPA -->
	
	<string name="obs_rotas">The information contained herein about the bus routes were provided by the responsible organs of each municipality</string>
	<string name="busca_label_onibus">Line</string>
	<string name="busca_label_rota">Route</string>
	<string name="busca_label_favoritos">Favourites</string>
	
	    <!-- LIST ROUTE -->
    
    <string name="num_onibus">Number of Bus: </string>
    <string name="dif_onibus">Diference between bus: </string>
    <string name="hora_inicio">Start Time: </string>
    <string name="hora_fim">End Time: </string>
	
</resources>